clientscommunication.com 2014-08-29

# Free worldwide SMS service

### Privacy Policy & Practice

**Gathering of your personal information**

clientscommunication.com may collect information about your visit to our web site, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with the service. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website or service you visit, such as your IP address, browser type, language and geographical location.

Furthermore, in order to operate the Service, you understand and agree that clientscommunication.com stores, processes and maintains your messages and other data related to the uses of our service.

**Log Files**

Like many other websites, clientscommunication.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small text file that are placed on your hard disk by a Web page server for the purpose of facilitating and enhancing your communications and interaction with that Web site.

Cookies contain information that can later be read by the web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

clientscommunication.com relies on cookies to store your preferences and other information on the material where the application is set up in order to save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information.

For example, your user ID may be stored in a cookie that will remain on the material you use to access the Service after you sign out each application user session. This cookie allows your user ID to be pre-populated, so that you will only need to type your password the next time you sign in. clientscommunication.com never uses cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent or stored in a cookie.

**Third Party Cookies**

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on clientscommunication.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

clientscommunication.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Enforcement of this Privacy Notice**

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Notice, you should first contact us.

**Changes to this Privacy Notice**

As our Service evolves, our Privacy Notice will also undergo changes. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to make changes to this Notice at any time. We encourage you to check our Privacy Notice periodically to keep informed of how clientscommunication.com is protecting your information.

WE DO NOT ALLOW any unsolicited SMS, spam or illegal sms from our site. clientscommunication.com is tracking every single user who uses this free service. This means that all transactions are recorded and will be use against who violate and abuse the service.
